Guide to the Jerome Zerbe Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Jerome Zerbe photographs and papers
1880-2009
GEN MSS 1122
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
27.51
(158 boxes)
Zerbe, Jerome, 1904-1988
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Frederick R. Koch, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 157 (audiovisual materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Biographical / Historical
Jerome Zerbe (Yale 1928) was an American photographer. He specialized in photographing celebrities and society events, most notably as the house photographer at the El Morocco club in New York, and influenced the work of later paparazzi. In addition to his work as a photographer, Zerbe wrote society columns and during the Second World War served as Admiral Chester W. Nimitz's personal photographer.
Scope and Contents
The collection documents Jerome Zerbe's work as a photographer and chronicler of mid-twentieth century celebrities and society events. Photograph albums assembled by Zerbe span his time as a student at Yale in the 1920s, his brief time as an artist in Hollywood in the 1930s, and his long career as a society photographer and paparazzo, notably as the house photographer at the El Morocco nightclub in New York. The albums also document his naval service in the Pacific theater as Admiral Chester W. Nimitz's personal photographer during the Second World War. In addition to albums, photographs include loose prints and film negatives, most black and white. Zerbe's diaries include sometimes daily records of his work and social life, and span from his time at Yale to a few years before his death. Papers include subject files, often related to publishing projects, writings for Zerbe's society columns, clippings, correspondence, passports, and materials relating to Zerbe's home "Windsong" in Essex, Connecticut. Papers also include correspondence and other materials generated by Frederick R. Koch while he owned the collection from 1989 to 2013. Audiovisual materials consist of a recording of an interview with Zerbe.
Arrangement
Organized into four series: I. Photographs, circa 1880s-2000s. II. Diaries, 1925-1983. III. Papers, circa 1900s-2000s. IV. Audiovisual Materials, 1965.
Celebrities -- Pictorial works; Nightclubs -- New York (State) -- New York; Paparazzi -- United States; Photographers -- United States -- Archives; Socialites -- Pictorial works; World War, 1939-1945 -- Naval operations, American -- Pictorial works; Audiovisual materials; Black-and-white photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Film negatives; Photographic prints -- United States -- 20th Century; Photograph albums -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographers -- United States -- 20th Century; Koch, Frederick R. (Frederick Robinson); Zerbe, Jerome, 1904-1988; El Morocco (Nightclub: New York, N.Y.)
- Photographs, circa 1880s-2000s; Series I; 18.46; (142 boxes)
  - Photograph albums, circa 1900-2000s
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. I, Ohio, 1931 May-1934 June (Box 1)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. II, Ohio / New York / Detroit, 1931-1934 (Box 2)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. III, 1934 June 30-1935 Fall (Box 3)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Hollywood, 1935 (Box 4)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 1, Nos. 1-359, 1935-1936 (Box 5)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 2, Nos. 360-877, 1936 (Box 6)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 3, Nos. 878-1425, 1936-1937 (Box 7)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 4, Nos. 1426-1938, 1937 (Box 8)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 5, Nos. 1939-3513, 1937 (Box 9)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 7, Nos. 4085-4627, 1937-1938 (Box 10)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 8, Nos. 4628-5175, 1938 (Box 11)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 9, Nos. 5176-5736, 1938 (Box 12)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 10, Nos. 5737-6231, 1938-1939 (Box 13)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 11, Nos. 6232-6741, 1939 (Box 14)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 12, Nos. 6742-7253, 1939 (Box 15)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 13, Nos. 7254-7723, 1939 (Box 16)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 14, Nos. 7724-8210, 1939 (Box 17)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 15, Nos. 8211-8619, 1939-1940 (Box 158)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 16, Nos. 8620-9051, 1940 (Box 18)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 17, Nos. 9052-9467, 1940 (Box 19)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 18, Nos. 9468-9934, 1940 (Box 20)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 19, Nos. 9935-10502, 1940 (Box 21)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 20, Nos. 10503-11046, 1940-1941 (Box 22)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 21, Nos. 11047-11600, 1941 (Box 23)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 22, Nos. 11601-12235, 1941 (Box 24)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 23, Nos. 12236-12803, 1941-1942 (Box 25)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 24, Nos. 12804-13424, 1942 (Box 26)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 25, Nos. 13425-13829, 1942 (Box 27)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 26, Nos. 13830-14202, 1942-1943 (Box 28)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 27, Nos. 14203-14529, 1943 (Box 29)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 28, Nos. 14530-14772, 1943 (Box 30)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 29, Nos. 14773-15088, 1943-1944 (Box 31)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 30: Navy life, Bretteville and homes and their people, Port Chicago disaster, circa 1944 (Box 32)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 31: Navy, 1944 (Box 33)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 32: Navy, 1944-1945 (Box 34)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 33: Navy - Guam (G), 1944 (Box 35)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 34: Japan (J), Navy, 1945 (Box 36)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 35: End of Navy, San Francisco, Hollywood, New York, 1945 September-1946 May 10 (Box 37)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 36: Newport, Fire Island, Connecticut, Summer Spots, 1946 May-1946 July (Box 38)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 37: Houses and people and land, townscapes, Nantucket, Cape Cod, Southampton, Rhinebeck, Vanderbilt's Eagle's Nest, 1946 July 12-1946 October 1 (Box 39)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 38: Eagle's Nest, Knoedler, Zerbe's Exhibit @ French & Co., Widener Debut, circa 1946 (Box 40)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 39: New Orleans - architecture, Palm Beach, Georgetown, 1947 January 22 (Box 41)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 41: Rhinebeck, Annie's Debut (Larsen), Ford / Firestone wedding, Potter / Lucs wedding, Blevin - Davis Dance, Wagstaff, circa 1947 (Box 42)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 42: John Payson, Adams Dance, "Idle Hour Estate," Mortimer / Paley wedding, Nantucket, Eyre / Van Slyck wedding, Balsan Apt., St. Regis, 1947 July 20 (Box 43)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 43: Waldorf Plaza Balls, Powells party for Gielgud and Anderson Leigh Dance, Essex, 1947 October 2-1947 December (Box 44)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 44: Cukor Party @ "21," Met. Museum Fr. tapestry opening, Mus. of city of NY, Debuts and Deb Cotillion, Virginia Leigh Debut, 1947 (Box 45)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 45: Washington D.C. - National Symphony Benefit, Valentina's Russian Easter Party, St. Regis, Viennese Roof Re-opening, house warming weekend - Windsong, Yugoslavian royalty, Yale 20th, 1948 (Box 46)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 46: Nantucket, houses, architecture, Saratoga, Hollywood, Pasadena, San Francisco, Moscow Mule Party, Eve Warner Debut, 1948 July 3-1948 October (Box 47)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 47: St. Regis, Maisonette Reopening, Tuxedo Ball, Draper Exhibition, Knoedler Mill, Rogers Collection, Chas. James, Gibson Girl Ball - Plaza, 1948 October (Box 48)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 48: Larsens, Bermuda, Woolley Debut, "At Homes" for Cue France / Tour D'Argent, "Come As A Song" party., 1948 December 24-1949 May (Box 49)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 49: Versailles, South of France, du Barry Pavillion Arch. details and views, 1949 May (Box 50)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 50: David Bruces in Paris, Embassy Res. French Pavillions and Chateaux, Parisian hotels, Versailles, 1949 May-1949 June (Box 51)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 51: French chateaux, Paris, Mystic, Nantucket, Tuxedo Park, Weddings, Princeton, 1949 July-1949 September (Box 52)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 52: Soldier / Sailor Benefit, Weddings, Ann Larsen - Ritz engagement, Chicago, Palm Beach, Bal Masque, 1949 September-1949 December (Box 53)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 52A: Cleveland, Debuts - Sickles Gentry, Garbisch, White House Wedding, Russian Party and S-Neth, Greenbriar, Beaux-Arts, 1949 December-1950 June 1 (Box 54)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 53: Hollywood / Hedda Hopper, Cleveland, Debs, Katharine Hepburn, Govrell Opening, Europe, 1950 June 1-1950 October (Box 55)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 54: Versailles, Jamaica, Junior League and Knickerbocker Balls, Windsors - "Enchanted" and A.N.T.A., Chicago, D.C., A.N.T.A., 1950 October-1951 February (Box 56)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 55: A.N.T.A. party on Independence, Cincinnati, Boston - Phoenix Taliesin West and Fil. Wright, Stork Club, Greenbriar, Windsors, 1951 February-1951 June (Box 57)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 56: Indianapolis, Paris and France (Parties in Paris), Rome, 1951 May-1951 July (Box 58)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 57: Tivoli, Florence, Gogi's Larue, Bermuda, San Francisco, Hollywood, Rev. Hills, 1951 July-December (Box 59)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 58: Knickerbocker Ball, Germany, Rome, Greece, Spain, Deb. Cotillion, Jean Stein Party, Firestone Dance, Pen and Pencil, April in Paris Ball, 1951 December-1952 May (Box 60)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 59: French Wine Country, Anne Larsen / Gordon Ritz Wedding, St. Louis / Cleveland, Roy and Margot's 25th Anniversary, Hammerstein and Rodgers Party, 1952 May (Box 61)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 60: USS United States maiden voyage, Newport Debuts, Rockefeller Center Tour, Tallulah Bankhead, Pen and Pencil Benefit, Omaha, Palm Beach, Miami, 1952 July 3-1952 November 13 (Box 62)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 61: Dallas Debuts - Barbara Warner, El Morocco, Jamaica, D.C. -Inaugural Ball, London, 1952 November-1953 April (Box 63)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 62: London (Faribanks), Germany, SS America and Doria, Versailles, 1953 March-1953 July (Box 64)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 63: Venice (Peggy Guggenheim), France, Newport - Chas. Baskerville Exhibition, Rome, Erroll Flynn, 1953 July (Box 65)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 64: Spain, Paris - Berensons, Bruces, Ginger Rogers to Paris, Algiers, Susan Zerbe Larsen, Texas, Windsors, 1953 October (Box 66)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 65: Larsen Christmas with Baby Susan, Bal Des Roses, Goddard Gala, Jamaica, Firestone - Willis Wedding, Florida - C.Z. Guest, April in Paris - Waldorf, 1953 December 24 (Box 67)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 66: Chicago and Lake Forest, Versailles, La Jolla, Hollywood (Hedda's), Mrs. Bruce, San Francisco Party - Zerbe, Dixon - Ryan Wedding, Victor Borge, Irish - Welsh castles, 1954 May 15 (Box 68)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 67: Paris, French Chateaux Wine Country, Hunt Hartford's New York apartment, Mrs. Heart's apartment, San Francisco Opera, Fleishman Party for Tallulah Bankhead, 1954 June 24 (Box 69)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 68: Miami, Palm Beach, Palfrey - Hutton Wedding, Crusade Ball, Biltmore, Bea Lillie - London, France, Bavaria, Jamaica, Islands, Panama, 1954 June 24 (Box 70)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 69: Istanbul, Windsong, Athens, Rome (Ingrid Bergman), Paris, Versailles, "Night In Bagdad" Party, Valley Ranch Wyoming, 1955 May-1955 October (Box 71)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 70: Hollywood Hoppers, Gary Cooper, Dinner Dance, Vincent Prince House, San Francisco, Eliz. Guest Dance, Bal Des Roses Plaza (Grace Kelly), 1955 October (Box 72)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 71: France with Margot, Holland, Channing Hare Exhibition, Newport, Nantucket, Provincetown, Maine, Mexico City, Barbados, Trinidad, 1956 April 11 (Box 73)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 72: Dallas Symphony, Borge, Essex, Gishes, Mixcoac, Acapulco, Bachelors Ball - Ambassador, Goodman - Malloy Wedding, Florida and Caribbean, April In Paris Ball, 1956 October-1957 July (Box 74)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 73: T&C College, Tour of Europe - France, Italy, Switzerland, Holland, Germany, Zerbe's Accident, Imperial Waif Ball, L.A., Andrew Hepburn, Jamaica, Bachelors Ball, 1957 July-1958 February (Box 75)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 74: Palm Beach, San Francisco, Mamoulian House, Beverly Hills, Havana, Montreal, France (S. Maugham), Crawford / Steele Apartment, 1958 February-1958 September 28 (Box 76)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 75: Astor Ball, Washington D.C., Montreal, Aly Khan Dinner, Stein / Van Den Heuvel Wedding, Jo Hughes Party, Carlyle Luchow, Hedda Vodka, Lisbon, 1958 September 30-1959 April (Box 77)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 76: Italy, Hearst / Hearndon Reception, Paris and Windsors in France, A.C. Moulin, Denmark, Sweden, Ireland, Ros. Russell at Larsens, 1959 November (Box 78)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 77: Hughes Dinner - Carlyle, Kennedy Found. Party, Weddings, Celebs - Crawford, Merman, France, Nantucket, 1959 December (Box 79)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 78: Pan Am / Idlewild, Jamaica and Barbados, Frank Hunter Party - "21 Brands," Many Hollywood Celebrities Throughout, El Morocco's Closing Nights, 1960 August (Box 80)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 79: Nassau, Palm Beach, Balls and Dances, Revlon Salon Opening, Celebrity Party, Palma Di Majorca and Onassis, Kelly and Ranier, Callas, 1961 March-1961 September (Box 81)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 80: Clyde Newhouse Party, April in Paris Ball, Party at Jules Steins, Bloomingdale's Party, Six-Week Cruise and Tour with Jon Larsen, Gloria Swanson, Chas. Addams, 1961 October-1962 May (Box 82)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 81: French Chateaux and Trip with Larsens, Scandinavia - Much Architecture, Tony Awards dinner at Americana, April in Paris, 1962 May 31 (Box 83)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 82: Nassau, Jamaica - Noel Coward's, Palm Beach, Belgium, France, Ireland, Italy, Munich, 1963 February-1963 August (Box 84)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 83: Bavaria, Newport, Scandinavia, Italy, Tokyo, Hong Kong, Round Hill, Luchow Party, Zerbe's Party for King Hussein of Jordan, 1963 August 7-1964 April (Box 85)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 84: Personalities, Nassau, Palm Beach, Caracas, Christmas 1970 in Wayzata, circa 1964-1970 (Box 86)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 85: Windsors, Berlin 1971, Reopening of El Morocco, US and Europe, 1959-1973 (Box 87)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. 86: Travel, Larsen Holiday and Birthdays, 50th Anniversary, Old 1940s Pictures at end, Last Volume (no # - Last - "86"), 1929-1979 (Box 88)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. A: Key West / Charleston, circa 1940s (Box 89)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. B: Nantucket (N.D.), circa 1940s (Box 90)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. C: Essex, Bermuda, New York City, 1947-1948 (Box 91)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. D: Windsong, 1950 January-1966 (Box 92)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. E: Mixed People / Essex (N.D.), 1950s (Box 93)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. F: Russia, 1965-1969 (Box 94)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. G: Palaces and Houses, Miami, Ireland, Madrid, 1966 (Box 95)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. H: England, 1966-1971 (Box 96)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. I: European Tours, 1969 (Box 97)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. J: France and Chateaux, 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 98)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. K: Planning of Connecticut Home (Windsong) from Aquisition of Land, 1938-1949 (Box 99)
    - Jerome Zerbe Vol. L: Essex / Windsong - END, undated (Box 100)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Personal Clippings #4, 1939 July (Box 101)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Personal Clippings #5, 1941 May-1948 August (Box 102)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Personal Clippings #6, 1948 August (Box 103)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Personal Clippings #7, 1952 September-1959 (Box 104)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Personal Clippings #8, 1959 February-1963 March (Box 105)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Personal Clippings #9, 1963-1968 (Box 106)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Advertisements #1, circa 1940s (Box 107)
    - Jerome Zerbe, Advertisements #2, 1940s-1950s (Box 108)
    - Jerome Zerbe, family album, circa 1900-1930s (Box 109)
    - Jerome Zerbe, family and travel albums, 1921-1924 (Box 110)
    - Jerome Zerbe, family and travel albums, 1924-1929 (Box 111)
    - Jerome Zerbe, family and travel albums, 1929-1930 (Box 112)
    - Prints and papers removed from albums, 1930s-2000s
      - Photographs removed from albums, circa 1930s-1960s; 8 folders (Box 113)
      - Jerome Zerbe and Josephine Dunn, circa 1935 (Box 113)
      - Photographs removed from Vol. 34, Navy, 1945 (Box 113)
      - Photographs removed from Vol. L, Windsong, 1937-1938 (Box 113)
      - Fireman's Ball prints, undated (Box 113)
      - Loose prints not from albums, undated (Box 113)
      - Reproductions, 1990s-2000s (Box 113)
      - Ephemera removed from albums, undated, 1987 (Box 113)
      - Cafe Society photograph list, 1989 (Box 113)
      - Empty envelopes from prints restored to albums, undated; 3 folders (Box 113)
      - Ephemera removed from books, 1966-2003; 3 folders (Box 113)
      - Prints of Navy photographs, circa 1943 (Box 114)
  - Prints, circa 1880s-1970s
    - Mixed subjects, circa 1880s-1970s
      - Non-navy, 1930s-1970s (Box 115)
      - Non-navy, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 116)
      - Mixed, 1930s-1950s (Box 117)
      - Mixed, circa 1900s-1970s (Box 118 (Oversize))
      - Family photographs and prints used in Happy Times, circa 1880s-1940s (Box 119)
      - Mrs. Tobin Clarks "House on Hill" near San Francisco, 1943 (Box 119)
    - Navy, 1944-1945
      - Wartime, 1944-1945 (Box 120)
      - Wartime, 1944-1945 (Box 121)
    - Framed photographs, 1940s (Box 122)
    - Fontaines de la Concorde, Paris, circa 1950s (Box 123)
    - The Duke and Duchess of Windsor at The Plaza greet Jerome, circa 1940 (Box 123)
    - To Jerome from Hedda (Hopper), undated (Box 123)
    - Contact print of two photographs of Steve Reeves, used in "Happy Times," p. 44, undated (Box 123)
    - Larsen family portraits, circa 1920s-1960s (Box 124)
    - Photograph of Bust, Jerome Zerbe of Cleveland and New York from the head, by William McVey, done in 1932, destroyed 1942 (Box 124)
  - Negatives, 1930s-1970s
    - Travel, 1937-1970s
      - U.S.A. by state, California - Maryland, 1940s
        Conditions Governing Access
        Non-safety film. Not available for research.
      - U.S.A. by state, Mississippi - Virginia, 1937-1947
      - Palm Beach, 1939-1947
      - Caribbean, 1939-1950
      - France, 1940s - circa 1952
        Scope and Contents
        Includes Chateau of les Mesnuls and Paris
      - Paris, 1940s-1952
        Includes architecture, monuments, and city views of England and Germany from air and boat trips to Europe.
      - General Travel Europe, 1950s-1960s (Box 125)
        Includes Austria, Belgium, Denmark, England, Finland, Germany, Holland, Russia, and Sweden.
      - General Travel, 1950s-1970s (Box 126)
        Includes Italy, Portugal, the Mediterranean, Greece, the Middle East, cruises, and plane tours.
      - General Travel, France, 1950s-1970s (Box 127)
      - General Travel, Caribbean, 1950s-1970s (Box 128)
        Includes Antiqua, the Bahamas, Barbados, Haiti, Jamaica, St. Croix, St Thomas, Tobago, and Trinidad.
      - General Travel, The Americas, 1950s-1970s (Box 129)
        Includes the U.S.A., Canada, Costa Rica, Cuba, Mexico, Panama, Puerto Rico, San Salvador, and Venezuela.
    - People, 1930s-1970s
      - A-B, 1935-1940s
      - C- Hearst, 1935-1940s
      - Hesse - Mc/Mac - Maxwell, 1935-1940s
        Non-safety film. Not available for research..
      - Mayor - Ryan, 1935-1940s
      - St. George - Vanderbilt, 1935-1940s
      - Vanderbilt (Cont.) - Windsor, 1935-1940s
      - Woodward -Z, and unidentified, circa 1935-1940s
      - A-J, circa 1952-1979 (Box 130)
      - K-Z, circa 1952-1979 (Box 131)
      - Family and self including some copy negatives, circa 1930s-1970s (Box 132)
    - Events, 1935-1970s
      - Individuals' parties, lunches, and weekends (by honored or giver): A-Max, 1935-1951
      - Individuals' parties, lunches, and weekends (by honored or giver): Mes-Z, 1935-1940s
      - Large parties, balls and benefits (by organization), Worlds Fair 1940, 1935-1940s
        Also includes the 1940 Worlds Fair.
      - Theater openings, exhibitions, and gallery openings, 1935-1950
      - Debuts and weddings, 1940s-1950s
      - Events, 1939-1970s (Box 133)
    - Color Negatives, 1940s-1970s
      - Architecture/cities/travel, 1940s-1970s (Box 134)
        Algiers-Puerto Rico
      - Architecture/cities/travel, 1940s-1970s (Box 135)
        Includes Russia-Wales, cruise ships, color internegatives, people, private houses and apartments, Larsen family, self, Windsong and other subjects.
    - Houses and apartments, 1940s-1970s
      - By owner's name (includes prints), and unidentified, 1940s-1952
      - Europe by owner's name, 1950s-1970s (Box 136)
      - U.S.A., the Caribbean, and Venezuela by owner's names, 1950s-1970s (Box 137)
    - Navy, 1944-1945
      - WWII, Pacific, 1944-1945
      - WWII, Pacific, 1944-1945
    - Miscellaneous, 1930s-1950s
      - Marked by Zerbe to decipher and identify, storms, Zerbe's apartments, Larsen family, 1940-1950
      - Miscellaneous subjects, including El Morocco, theater, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 138)
    - Clubs and restaurants, 1930s-1940s
      - Numbered and incomplete, 1935-1939
      - Odd El Morocco, Ciro's, Colony, Waldorf, and others, 1930s-1940s
    - Happy Times, 1930s-1940s
      - Hollywood, early themes, el Morrocco and others, 1935-1940s
      - Incomplete collection of negatives used in Happy Times, 1930s-1940s (Box 139)
    - Other negatives, 1930s-1990s
      - Copy negatives, circa 1930s-1970s (Box 140)
      - du Barry negatives, circa 1963 (Box 141)
        Separated Materials
        Non-safety film negatives have been removed.
      - Kodak Negative Album of Zerbe negatives with Fred Koch correspondence, 1940s-1990s (Box 141)
      - Empty negative sleeves, undated (Box 141)
- Diaries, 1925-1983; Series II; 2.67; (5 boxes)
  - Diary, Yale, 1925-1926 (Box 142)
  - Diary, Yale, 1926-1927 (Box 142)
  - Diary, Yale, 1928 (Box 142)
  - Diary, 1931 (Box 142)
  - Diary, 1934 (Box 142)
  - Diary, 1935 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1936 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1937 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1938 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1939 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1940 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1941 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1942 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1943 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1944 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1946 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1947 (Box 143)
  - Diary, 1948 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1949 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1950 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1951 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1952 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1953 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1954 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1955 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1956 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1957 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1958 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1959 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1960 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1961 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1962 (Box 144)
  - Diary, 1963 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1964 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1965 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1967 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1968 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1969 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1970 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1971 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1972 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1973 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1974 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1975 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1976 (Box 145)
  - Diary, 1977 (Box 146)
  - Diary, 1978 (Box 146)
  - Diary, 1979 (Box 146)
  - Diary, 1980 (Box 146)
  - Diary, 1981 (Box 146)
  - Diary, 1982 (Box 146)
  - Day planner, 1982 (Box 146)
  - Day planner, 1983 (Box 146)
  - Windsong guest book, 1948-1956 (Box 146)
  - Windsong guest book, 1956-1966 (Box 146)
- Papers, circa 1900s-2000s; Series III; 6.17; (10 boxes)
  - Clippings, photographs, correspondence, notes and other research materials, 1910s-2000s
    - Pavillions around Paris, 1940s-1960s; 3 folders (Box 147)
    - Mostly du Barry, 1950s-1970s; 2 folders (Box 147)
    - Lady Mendl, 1940s-1970s (Box 147)
    - Great Parties, circa 1960s-1970s; 3 folders (Box 147)
    - Laura Corrigan, 1930s-1970s (Box 147)
    - Letters of Madame du Barry, undated (Box 147)
    - Aristotle Onassis, undated (Box 147)
    - For Book, 1910s-1960s; 2 folders (Box 147)
    - Koch Choices, circa 2000s (Box 147)
    - Interveiw transcript, 1983 (Box 147)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 147)
    - Time INC. file, 1942-1977 (Box 148)
    - War, Navy Department, 1945-1998 (Box 148)
    - Foolishness, undated (Box 148)
    - Marion Davies, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Vanderbilts, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Jekle, 1940s-1950s (Box 148)
    - Argylls, 1960s (Box 148)